<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>DeKalb Chamber of Commerce Events Newswire</title><link>http://dekalb.org</link><description>News related to DeKalb Chamber of Commerce</description><copyright>(c) 2015, DeKalb Chamber of Commerce All Rights Reserved.</copyright><ttl>5</ttl><item><title>Who's Afraid Of Virginia Woolf 9/24/2015 7:30 PM - 10/3/2015 10:30 PM</title><description>NIU's Procuction of Who's Afraid of Virigina Woolf?
Written By Edward Albee

This 1962 dramatic comedy by Edward Albee examines the vitriolic dismemberment
of the marriage of middle-aged couple, Martha and George. George is a burned-out
associate history professor and Martha is simply an unhappy shrew, and they have grown
tired of only pushing each other’s buttons.
Late one evening, following a college faculty party where the alcohol has flowed freely,
they have invited an unwitting younger couple, Nick and Honey, as guests for a nightcap.
Nick is a new assistant professor of biology, and despite the late hour has readily
accepted the invitation, because he knows Martha’s father is the university president. As
jabs and nasty comments begin to flow as freely as the alcohol, it takes little time for the
older couple to draw the younger twosome into their frustrated relationship.
As hilarious as it is disturbing, Who’s Afraid of Virginia Woolf? presents one of theatre’s
most infamous dysfunctional couples. The dialogue in the first act of the play has been
hailed by some critics as some of the greatest in all of the American theatre.
Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf? won both the 1963 Tony Award for Best Play and the
1962–63 New York Drama Critics' Circle Award for Best Play. It is frequently revived on
the modern stage. The film adaptation was released in 1966, written by Ernest Lehman,
directed by Mike Nichols, and starred Richard Burton, Elizabeth Taylor, George Segal and
Sandy Dennis.

Performances
Thursday, September 24 7:30pm
Friday, September 25 7:30pm
Saturday, September 26 7:30pm
Sunday, September 27 2:00pm
Thursday, October 1 7:30pm
Friday, October 2 7:30pm
Saturday, October 3 2:00pm &amp; 7:30pm</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3624</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2015 13:29:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stop Motion Animation 9/26/2015 9:00 AM - 9/26/2015 12:00 PM</title><description>Create your own stop-motion animation video!  This class will cover the tools and techniques required to make short animations from real objects.  Over two classes, students will conceive and create their own stop-motion animation project, complete with characters, backdrops and effects.  Students will gain experience using cameras and digital video production techniques, as well as developing creativity as they design and produce their own story.  This course will be held at our Naperville campus and is recommended for ages 10 and up.  This is a 2-part class. The second class takes place on September 26th. 
Morning Session: 9:00am- 12.00pm OR Afternoon session 1.00pm-4.00pm       
$79 for 2-class session </description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3556</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2015 15:30:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>STEM Divas Robotics 9/26/2015 9:00 AM - 9/26/2015 1:00 PM</title><description>Join us for a fun LEGO Robotics class exploring the basic programming concepts, and introducing the functions of the LEGO Mindstorms robots. Learn from experienced female engineers how to design your own robot while exploring the role robots play in our life and how they can be used to solve real world problems. No prior experience with programming or robotics is needed.  Recommended ages 7 and up. 
$39 for one class session </description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3557</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2015 15:44:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Walk &amp; Roll for Mobility 9/26/2015 8:30 AM - 9/26/2015 11:30 AM</title><description>Are you ready to "Walk &amp; Roll"?

On Saturday, September 26, two independent, privately-owned physical therapy clinics will host "Walk &amp; Roll For Mobility," a 1.6 one-way walk along the DeKalb Nature Trail from Creative Therapeutics, 400 E. Hillcrest Drive in DeKalb, to Northern Rehab Physical Therapy Specialists 232 W. Lincoln Highway, DeKalb office. The event proceeds will benefit the Voluntary Action Center (VAC). Fun for the whole family – bikes, strollers, walking sticks, and skates welcome!

“Walk &amp; Roll for Mobility” helps kick-off National Physical Therapy Month in October, and allows both independent clinics support a non-profit community organization. On event day, check in begins at 8:30am at Creative Therapeutics; a walking stick demonstration will be at 8:40am; a dynamic warm up is at 8:50am; raffle prize winners are drawn at 8:55am; and the walk kicks off at 9:00 am. Walk, ride, or roll from Creative Therapeutics to Northern Rehab along the DeKalb Nature Trail. Enjoy live music and refreshments upon arrival at Northern Rehab. Walk round-trip or one-way at this fundraising event; a VAC bus will be available for optional return transport back to Creative Therapeutics. 

Pre-registration is suggested; those who pre-register by Sept. 23 will be entered into a drawing for various prizes! Call 815.758.5508 to register. A suggested donation of $5.00 per individual or $10 per family will be collected the day of the event upon check-in. All funds will go directly to the Voluntary Action Center (VAC).
While Northern Rehab and Creative Therapeutics are friendly competitors in business, as independent small businesses they share many values. As practitioners they connect with their patients and provide personal and individualized care. Both companies encourage the community to understand that they have the right to choose where you receive care. 
Hosted by Northern Rehab and Creative Therapeutics – your independent choices for physical therapy- we invite all of our past patients, friends and families, and businesses to participate and celebrate your independence and freedom to move at this fun, family event! 

For more information about “Walk &amp; Roll For Mobility”, please visit wholept.com or northernrehabpt.com.
</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3393</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2015 19:07:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Superhero 7K, 1K Walk &amp; Kids 1K run for LIVESTRONG at the YMCA 9/26/2015 3:30 PM - 9/26/2015 </title><description>Grab your best superhero costume, lace up your tennis shoes and run for a cause! Great event for the entire family! Proceeds raised will help fund the Y&amp;rsquo;s LIVESTRONG at the YMCA Cancer Survivor Program. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Race Day Schedule of Events &lt;br /&gt;
3:30pm-Kids 1K begins &lt;br /&gt;
4:30pm&amp;ndash; 1K Survivor Walk (Free) &lt;br /&gt;
5:15pm&amp;ndash; Superhero 7K &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
We encourage all to show their spirit and wear your favorite Superhero costumes! &lt;br /&gt;
Superhero 7K / 1K Walk / Kids 1K: Registration fee: $30; Survivor 1K Walk - FREE &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Superhero 7K, 1K Walk and Kids 1K Pre-Registration Race Day registration will be available in the YMCA Sports Center from 4:00-5:15 pm *Registration fee includes event t-shirt if registered by Sept 14 Survivors walk FREE!</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3445</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2015 18:45:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Toon into Energy 9/26/2015 9:00 AM - 9/26/2015 2:00 PM</title><description>Meet special guest Tom Fowler!

Students Will – 
-	Experience a day of hands-on learning
-	Interact with STEM experts and Illustrators
-	Create science-themed comics
-	Work in teams to solve art and energy challenges

Event check-in begins at 8:30 A.M.
This program is recommended for children grade 6 and up.
Register at: stemread.com 
</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3591</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2015 18:53:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Unity Hospice Veteran's History Project 9/28/2015 8:00 AM - 10/2/2015 9:00 PM</title><description>Unity Hospice of Western Illinois  invites veterans to share their story of wartime to be submitted to the Library of Congress through the Veterans History Project.

Unity Hospice of Western Illinois is inviting veterans in the Western Illinois suburbs to share their stories of wartime to be submitted to the Library of Congress through a nationally-recognized program called the Veterans History Project. One of the world’s most respected research and cultural institutions, the Library of Congress will preserve these stories for future generations so they can better understand American history and the realities of war.

Interested veterans are invited to contact Unity Hospice to schedule an appointment to share their personal stories in the form of unedited video recorded interviews.  Interviews will be conducted during the week of September 28 – October 2, 2015. Read more about the Veterans History Project on their website at http://www.loc.gov/vets/.

For more information about the Veterans History Project in your community or to schedule a time to share your story, please contact Unity Hospice Director of Program Development Brenda McGarvey at (618) 954-6114 or volunteers@unityhospice.com.

Unity Hospice of Western Illinois
1201 S. 7th Street, Suite 101
Rochelle, IL  61068
</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3579</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2015 14:34:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Small Business Finance and Resource Event 9/30/2015 5:30 PM - 9/30/2015 8:30 PM</title><description>Small Business Owners - Connect with resources who can help you grow your business: business planning, financing, marketing, social media, accounting, insurance and more. Network with fellow entreprenuers.  Connect with local organizations that support small businesses. Refreshments provided. Free registration: www.accionchicago.org/dekalb.</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3553</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2015 19:42:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DeKalb County Culture Business Roundtable 9/30/2015 11:00 AM - 9/30/2015 1:00 PM</title><description>You're invited to the DeKalb County Culture BUSINESS ROUNDTABLE

Have you wondered how impactful DeKalb County's
Arts &amp; Entertainment Industry is to our Economy?

Learn from DeKalb County's 
Arts, Entertainment &amp; Tourism Industry Leaders


Featuring a panel of participants including:


Debbie Armstrong-
Executive Director
DeKalb County Convention &amp; Visitors Bureau 

Brad Hoey 
Director of Campus Communications
Northern Illinois University
 
Alex Nerad
Executive Director
Egyptian Theatre
 
Representative
NIU Convocation Center

When and Where

Time:11:00 AM - 1:00 PM


Date: Wednesday, September 30th
 
Location: Northern Illinois University, Convocation Center
 
**Please visit our website, www.dcedc.org for updates throughout the reservation process**
</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3596</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2015 14:45:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DCBDA Golf Outing 10/2/2015 12:00 PM - 10/2/2015 6:00 PM</title><description>DeKalb County Building &amp; Development Association Golf Outing. Registration @ 12 pm. Shotgun start @ 1 pm. Please turn the form in by October 1st.</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3592</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2015 15:35:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>One and Only Ivan Night with NIU STEM Read 10/2/2015 4:00 PM - 10/2/2015 6:00 PM</title><description>Free with admission
Enjoy an evening of crafts and activities based off of The One and Only Ivan.</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3589</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 18:06:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pet Blessing 10/4/2015 1:00 PM - 10/4/2015 </title><description>St. Paul’s Episcopal Church invites the public to bring their favorite four-legged friends and other creatures to a Pet Blessing Celebration, Sunday, October 4 at 1:00 p.m. at 900 Normal Road in DeKalb.  
	The Pet Blessing is traditionally celebrated the first Sunday in October on the Feast Day of St. Francis of Assisi, who was known for his affection toward animals of all kinds.  The public is invited to bring their pets for a celebration of their life, as well as a personal blessing from Rev. Amy Fallon, Director of Grace Place Ministries, NIU Campus.  Photographs may also be brought to honor pets that prefer not to travel.
	The celebration will be held in front of St. Paul’s Episcopal Church, located at 900 Normal Road in DeKalb.  </description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3594</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2015 19:38:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Normal Heart 10/8/2015 7:30 PM - 10/11/2015 9:30 </title><description>NIU's Production of The Normal Heart written by Larry Kramer
From the Foreword to The Normal Heart: Larry Kramer's The Normal Heart is a play in the great
tradition of Western drama. In taking a burning social issue and holding it up to public and private
scrutiny so that it reverberates with the social and personal implications of that issue, The Normal
Heart reveals its origins in the theater of Sophocles, Euripides, and Shakespeare. In his moralistic
fervor, Larry Kramer is a first cousin to nineteenth-century Ibsen and twentieth-century Odets and other
radical writers of the 1930s. Yet, at the heart of The Normal Heart, the element that gives this powerful
political play its essence, is love—love holding firm under fire, put to the ultimate test, facing and
overcoming our greatest fear: death. I love the ardor of this play, its howling, its terror and its kindness.
It makes me very proud to be its producer and caretaker. — JOSEPH PAPP

Performances:
Thursday, October 8 7:30 pm
Friday, October 9 7:30 pm
Saturday, October 10 2:00 pm
Saturday, October 10 7:30 pm
Sunday, October 11 2:00 </description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3634</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2015 17:22:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mental Health First Aid Certification 10/9/2015 8:00 AM - 10/9/2015 5: PM</title><description>You are more likely to encounter a person in an emotional crisis than someone in cardiac arrest. Would you know what to do?

group of students
Mental Health First Aid is an evidenced-based public education program that teaches the key skills needed to help someone with a mental health problem or crisis. This nationally-recognized certification focuses on the skills that can be used until professional help is obtained. </description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3648</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2015 00:47:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Member Roundtable - Safety throughout the Workplace 10/9/2015 8:30 AM - 10/9/2015 9:30 AM</title><description>Join us as we have members discuss safety concerns in the workplace. From internet safety, personal security, credit card concerns, insurance and more. Come to learn, or share your expertise as we have an open discussion. Registration is needed, but this is a free members only event. </description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3627</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2015 12:59:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kishwaukee Symphony Orchestra's Fall Concert: Voilà Viola 10/10/2015 7:30 PM - 10/10/2015 9:00 PM</title><description>The KSO will perform its Fall Concert: Voilà Viola, on Saturday, Oct. 10, at 7:30 pm, in the Boutell Memorial Concert Hall inside the Music Building, Northern Illinois University, DeKalb. There will be a free pre-concert lecture beginning at 6:30, in the Recital Hall. This concert will feature the Brandenburg Concerto No. 6, by Johann Sebastian Bach; Der Schwanendreher, by Paul Hindemith, with Anthony Devroye, viola; and The Enigma Variations, by Edward Elgar. This concert is supported in part by the Kishwaukee Symphony Associates.

All seats are general admission (no reserved seating). Individual ticket prices are $15 for adults, $10 for seniors 62 and over, $10 for students, and $5 for children under 12. Season tickets may be purchased at special prices for the four regular concerts of the season. Season ticket prices are $50 for adults, $35 for seniors, $35 for students, and $18 for children under 12. </description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3610</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 13:54:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>1940s Hangar Swing Dance - USO Fundraiser 10/10/2015 7:30 PM - 10/10/2015 11:30 PM</title><description>Dance, dance, dance!
Step back in time Saturday, October 10th, to the 1940s for a vintage USO hangar dance presented by the EAA DeKalb Chapter 241 at DeKalb Taylor Municipal Airport Community Hangar.

The Lakes Area Swing Band will provide music for the evening and a free swing dance lesson, donated by Carl and Karrie, will begin at 7:30 p.m. that evening.  Doors will open at 7:00 p.m. prior to the lesson.  Look smart in your vintage garb for the BEST DRESSED and DANCE contests that will be held during the evening.  

Tickets are AVAILABLE THAT NIGHT AT THE DOOR for $12.00 CASH ONLY.  Proceeds benefit the USO.  Bottled water will be available for purchase.  NO ALCOHOL ALLOWED. Please follow the link below to Facebook for additional information on the dance.</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3575</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2015 15:14:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Business After Hours - Line-X and C.O.P.S 10/13/2015 5:00 PM - 10/13/2015 7:00 PM</title><description>Join us for our afterhours at 2 local members. Line-X of Sycamore and C.O.P.S both have unique facilities to take a look at and network with other members. Maple Park Special Olympics will be on hand selling hats. Local police will be there to highlight vehicles. Rifle vendor on hand. Raffling off a firearm and gun vault (with valid FOID card). Plenty of food and cold beverages. </description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3628</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2015 13:28:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Open House  10/13/2015 5:00 PM - 10/13/2015 7:00 PM</title><description>C.O.P.S., Inc and LINE-X of Greater Illinois want you to come on by and say Hi. Food and Beverages will be provided. Everyone gets a FREE PAIR of shooting glasses while supplies last. Also, we will be GIVING AWAY a Hi-Point .380 Home Security Pack. Includes pistol and safe. (must have valid FOID card to be eligible) We are hoping you'll stop by and hang out for a while. Check out the store, get questions answered. Anybody and everybody is welcome. Representatives from the Special Olympics will be present as well. Bring the kids to check out a Police Car!</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3641</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2015 21:57:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Grand Opening of Country Financial Downtown DeKalb 10/15/2015 3:00 PM - 10/15/2015 6:00 PM</title><description>Grand Opening of Country Financial Downtown DeKalb with agents Gavin Wilson and Dean Miller.  Food/refreshments, give-away, raffle, and fun.  Also collecting donations for the Red Cross. </description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3621</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2015 20:04:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Let's Make A Difference, Autism Awarness Fundraiser for Opportunity House 10/15/2015 4:00 PM - 10/15/2015 7:00 PM</title><description>&lt;p style="text-align: left;"&gt;&lt;img alt="" style="height: 662px; width: 556px;" src="http://www.dekalb.org/external/wcpages/wcmedia/images/Opportunity%20House%20Fundraiser.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p  style="text-align: center;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 41pt; font-family: century schoolbook,serif; color: #ffc000;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3597</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2015 15:06:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>STEMfest  10/17/2015 10:00 AM - 10/17/2015 5:00 PM</title><description>Save the Date for STEMfest!
STEMfest is the Midwest’s premier festival for celebrating Science, Technology, Engineering, and Math (STEM). Explore hundreds of hands-on exhibits. Meet STEM students, faculty, professionals, and sci-fi writers. Win fabulous prizes in our video and writing competitions. Free and open to the visitors of all ages! No advanced registration required. 
</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3478</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2015 20:54:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lehan Drugs Daisy Dash 10/18/2015 9:00 AM - 10/18/2015 11:00 AM</title><description>&lt;img width="609" height="960" alt="" style="height: 628px; width: 382px;" src="http://www.dekalb.org/external/wcpages/wcmedia/images/daisydash-poster.jpg" width="609" height="960" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 20px;"&gt;Register Here:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://daisydash5k.itsyourrace.com/register/"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt;https://daisydash5k.itsyourrace.com/register/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3619</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 20:38:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Breakfast Briefings at Kishwaukee College 10/20/2015 7:45 AM - 10/20/2015 9:30 AM</title><description>Attract Quality Talent with Creative Marketing with Brian Oster

Your Marketing – website, recruiting brochure, tradeshow booth, etc. – all leave a perception in the eye of the viewer.  What does yours say?  Are potential top-notch employees being turned off by what they see?  This interactive session will help you examine your existing recruiting and marketing efforts, then provide you with immediate tools and short-term creative marketing tactics to begin changing your audience’s perception.  
 
Brian Oster is the Creative Director of OC Imageworks with more than 15 years experience in the advertising industry.  After working for a decade as an in-house marketer, he made the transition to agency work, allowing his creative ideas to flourish.  A student of his clients – always learning about their industries and their customers – he believes every marketing piece should influence and engage its specified audience.  Brian is a graduate of Augustana College with two Bachelor’s Degrees, and recently a graduate of the DeKalb Chamber Leadership Academy.  He was quickly accepted into the business community and immediately began demonstrating his servant leadership.  Brian is the committee chair for the Leadership Academy Advisory Committee, board member of Family Service Agency, and involved in several other area organizations.  

</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3642</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 19:03:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Speed Networking 10/20/2015 5:00 PM - 10/20/2015 7:00 PM</title><description>Join us for our next Speed Networking event. These are always very well-received and fill up quickly.  Practice your elevator speech and bring plenty of business cards and material to hand out. Cash bar and light appetizers. </description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3630</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2015 14:11:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>October Community Social: Pumpkin Painting Night 10/20/2015 4:30 PM - 10/20/2015 6:00 PM</title><description>Please come join us for our October Community Social.  The theme of this social is "all about fall" and we will be painting pumpkins with our families.  Please feel free to join us and take a tour of our wonderful center and see what it has to offer.      </description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3618</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 18:56:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stage Coach "Night of the Living Dead" show 10/22/2015 7:30 PM - 10/31/2015 </title><description>"Night of the Living Dead" blends thrilling horror mixed with touches of black humor to surround the audience in the action the has a shocking theatrical ending!This Stage Coach Players production brings all the fright of the cult classic to life with flesh-eating zombies and the people they trap in an isolated farm house. Special Halloween Night performances at 2:00 and 10:00 pm. Directed by Tim Ball. Tickets available online at stagecoachers.com or call the box office 815-758-1940</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3629</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2015 14:14:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Three Sisters 10/22/2015 7:30 PM - 10/31/2015 10:30 PM</title><description>Three Sisters
Written by Anton Chekhov
In a provincial town somewhere in Russia, the three Prozorov sisters—Olga, Masha and Irina—
and their brother Andrei, live in the large, beautiful house they inherited from their father.
Transplanted from Moscow eleven years earlier when the father, a brigadier general, took
command of an artillery unit in the garrison town, they are very conscious of their superior
status, education, refinement and taste.
On the one year anniversary of their father's death, they now long to escape. They
have become acutely aware of their dreary backwoods existence, stranded amongst
small town folk with no ambition or appreciation of the finer things they have deluded
themselves into remembering of the bright, thriving city they left as children.
Although they can pack up their worldly possessions and leave at any time, they will not
and perhaps simply cannot. They instead wallow in lethargy, made bearable only by the
visits of officers from the nearby artillery post, the only locals who are of their class.
However, the visitations soon fuel love affairs, flared tempers and deadly duels and turn
the proper Prozorov home into a place where anything can happen.
In Three Sisters, Russian playwright, Anton Chekhov conveys the wasting away of the upper
class in a coarse environment, but with an incomparable ability to subtly demonstrate the
psychic and spiritual costs of inaction. Three Sisters is considered a masterpiece of world
literature and is presented in repertoire by theatre companies across the globe.
Performances
Thursday, October 22 7:30pm
Friday, October 23 7:30pm
Saturday, October 24 7:30pm
Sunday, October 25 2:00pm
Thursday, October 29 7:30pm
Friday, October 30 7:30pm
Saturday, October 31 2:00pm &amp; 7:30pm</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3625</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2015 13:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2015 ATHENA Reception 10/27/2015 6:00 PM - 10/27/2015 8:00 PM</title><description>&lt;span style="font-family: segoe ui;"&gt;2015 ATHENA &amp;amp; Women of Accomplishment Reception. The ATHENA recognition is a national program sponsored locally by the DeKalb Chamber of Commerce, DEKALB SYCAMORE Chevrolet Cadillac GMC and the Daily Chronicle. This is the 26th Anniversary of the DeKalb Chamber of Commerce ATHENA Awards program.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt -2.15pt;"&gt;2015 ATHENA nominees:&lt;o:p _rdeditor_exists="1"&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt -2.15pt;"&gt;Debra Boughton &amp;ndash; NIU Athletics&lt;o:p _rdeditor_exists="1"&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt -2.15pt;"&gt;Carme Gregory &amp;ndash; H&amp;amp;R BLOCK Premium&lt;o:p _rdeditor_exists="1"&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt -2.15pt;"&gt;Terri Lehan Hettel &amp;ndash; Lehan Drugs&lt;o:p _rdeditor_exists="1"&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt -2.15pt;"&gt;Joanne Kantner &amp;ndash; Kishwaukee College&lt;o:p _rdeditor_exists="1"&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt -2.15pt;"&gt;Nancy Teboda &amp;ndash; Children&amp;rsquo;s Learning Center&lt;o:p _rdeditor_exists="1"&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt -2.15pt;"&gt;&lt;o:p _rdeditor_exists="1"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: segoe ui;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt -2.15pt;"&gt;2015 Women of Accomplishment nominees:&lt;o:p _rdeditor_exists="1"&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt -2.15pt;"&gt;Sue Guio &amp;ndash; retired from City of DeKalb&lt;o:p _rdeditor_exists="1"&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt -2.15pt;"&gt;Barbara Samulowitz &amp;ndash; retired from Clairol&lt;o:p _rdeditor_exists="1"&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt -2.15pt;"&gt;Mary Beth Van Buer &amp;ndash; retired from NIU&lt;o:p _rdeditor_exists="1"&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3595</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2015 20:18:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CSA Sinfonia Concert 10/28/2015 7:30 PM - 10/28/2015 </title><description>Come hear the best high school musicians in the area perform in the Concert Hall at the NIU Music Building.  Linc Smelser directs the CSA Youth Sinfonia.  A reception will follow the performance.

This concert is free and open to the public.</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3598</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2015 17:00:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Holiday Hiring Event 10/28/2015 10:00 AM - 10/28/2015 1:00 PM</title><description>Need Extra Cash? Check out the Holiday Hiring Event on Wednesday, October 28 (10am-1pm) in the Kishwaukee College Art Gallery Atrium.  10 companies will be hiring for seasonal, temporary, part-time positions.  SAVE THE DATE!  </description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3622</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2015 20:48:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DCEDC Annual Dinner &amp; State of the County 10/29/2015 5:00 PM - 10/29/2015 8:30 PM</title><description>Please join us at the NIU Duke Ellington Ballroom for our Annual Dinner and State of the County Presentation with Governor Bruce Rauner delivering the keynote address. This is a member-sponsored event.

Members Advanced Reservations will be available now, through 09/30/2015 @ $100/pp.  Member Standard Pricing @ $125/pp will begin on 10/1/2015.  Online Reservations will be accepted.  We regret that we are unable to accept telephone, fax, email, or walk-in reservations to this event.

Reservations will be available to Non-Members on 10/1/2015 @ $150/pp through 10/22/2015, or until the event is sold out, which ever occurs first.  Reservations will be accepted online only.</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3617</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 15:18:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Food Security Summit 10/30/2015 9:00 AM - 10/30/2015 4:00 PM</title><description>The DeKalb County Food Security Council and Live Healthy DeKalb County will present its first Food Security Summit on October 30th at the Outreach Building. Our presenters, Linda Delimata, Toni Tollerud, Luke Shaefer and Northern Illinois Food Bank, will address the needs of those in poverty in DeKalb County. Save your spot by sending your $15.00 check payable to Live Healthy DeKalb County, 1 Kish Hospital Drive 60115 by October 23rd.</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3632</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2015 15:48:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spooktacular - Downtown DeKalb Trick-or-Treat 10/31/2015 1:00 PM - 10/31/2015 3:00 PM</title><description>&lt;p style="line-height: 115%;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 14px; font-family: arial;"&gt;Nestle and the DeKalb Chamber of Commerce present Spooktacular, a Downtown DeKalb Trick-or-Treating event.&amp;nbsp; Spooktacular will take place on Saturday, October 31&lt;sup&gt;st&lt;/sup&gt;, 2015 from 1:00-3:00 p.m. Bring the kids out for a safe, fun, trick-or-treating event.&amp;nbsp; Kids will enjoy trick-or-treating at over 30 downtown businesses and making a spooky craft at the creepy craft shack located inside the House Caf&amp;eacute;. New to the event this year; there will be a FREE 11:30 am showing of Hocus Pocus at the Egyptian Theatre!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 14px; font-family: arial;"&gt;For more information visit downtowndekalb.org/events or call 815.756.6306.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img alt="" style="width: 400px;" src="http://www.dekalb.org/external/wcpages/wcmedia/images/Spooktacular%20FB.jpg" /&gt;</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3616</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2015 20:12:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Measure for Measure 11/5/2015 7:30 PM - 11/8/2015 9:30 PM</title><description>NIU's Production of Measure for Measure written by William Shakespeare
Unexpectedly, the Duke of Vienna leaves his throne and appoints young Angelo to govern in his
absence. In response to seeing the moral decay around him, the newly appointed ruler resurrects an
old law that treats adultery as a capital crime. In principle, he is committed to the ideals behind this
law. In practice, real life and its complications interfere with the purity of his vision. Innocent victims
and collateral damage appear at his doorstep and in his heart. Measure for Measure has been
classified by scholars as a problem play “characterized by its complex and ambiguous tone, which
shifts violently between dark, psychological drama and more straightforward comic material.” Perhaps
it is the absence of easy answers that attracts us to this Shakespeare story.

Performances:
Thursday, November 5 @ 7:30 pm
Friday, November 6 @ 7:30 pm
Saturday, November 7 @ 2:00 pm
Saturday, November 7 @ 7:30 pm
Sunday, November 8 @ 2:00 </description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3635</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2015 17:23:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Dean Martin &amp; Jerry Lewis Tribute Show 11/7/2015 7:30 PM - 11/7/2015 10:30 PM</title><description>Dean Martin and Jerry Lewis were the hottest act in America during the early 50’s. Dean of course, the straight man, with a charming voice and Jerry the lovable goof ball added the comedy. Never have two artists captured the look, the sound, the very essence and chemistry of these two “Icons” more than Tome Stevens and Tony Lewis. You don’t want to miss this evening of unpredictable hysterical music and laughter! 
Both of these incredible performers have each had amazing success on their own. Tony spent the last 27 years performing in Australia and created a name for himself as the quintessential “Jerry Lewis Tribute Artist” selling out countless venues and earned respect as one of Australia’s best entertainers. Since his 1st appearance at the annual Dean Martin Festival in 1998, Tom Stevens has earned his title as “Best Dean Martin Tribute Artist.” Even Dean’s daughter, Deana said, “I’ve never seen anyone look and sound more like my Daddy!”  
</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3643</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2015 15:47:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>STEM jr. 11/7/2015 9:00 AM - 11/7/2015 12:00 PM</title><description>It’s never too early for STEM!  This class will introduce our younger students to the concepts of engineering and design with simple, hands-on activities and projects to stimulate their creative thinking. Working together to solve fun building challenges will boost students' confidence and innovation skills. Each student will leave with a project that they will be proud to have constructed   Parents are welcome to stay and participate along with the students!  Recommended for ages 7 and up. This is a 2-part class. The second class takes place on November 14th. 
$59 for 2-class session 
</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3559</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2015 16:31:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Join the Maker Movement: Arduinos  11/7/2015 9:00 AM - 11/7/2015 12:00 PM</title><description>An Arduino is a small programmable computer that can be used to automate just about anything, and they have become a staple of the maker movement.  In these classes students will make their own basic circuits and program the Arduinos to look for and respond to input from sensors and controls.  Some previous experience with electronics and programming is recommended for this course, but not required.  This course will be held at our Naperville campus, and is recommended for ages 12 and up.  This is a 2-part class. The second class takes place on November 14th. 
$79 for 2-class session </description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3560</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2015 16:32:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Celebrate Veterans Day - Pippa White - Women of War 11/11/2015 12:30 PM - 11/11/2015 </title><description>Celebrate Veterans Day...with a look back at the Civil War, as presenter Pippa White tells us stories about the women and men involved 150 years ago. </description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3612</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2015 20:32:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Celebrate Veterans Day - Pippa White - On Our Own Soil 11/11/2015 7:00 PM - 11/11/2015 </title><description>Celebrate Veterans Day...with a look back at the Civil War, as presenter Pippa White tells us stories about the women and men involved 150 years ago. On Your Own Soil ($10 fee)</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3615</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2015 20:44:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mom's Night Out 11/11/2015 7:00 PM - 11/11/2015 10:00 PM</title><description>The Lehan Drugs Mommy and Baby Support Team is hosting this event to bring our community together for a night out! We will be screening of the film "Milk." It is an amazing movie that brings a universal perspective on the politics, commercialization and controversies surrounding birth and infant feeding over the canvas of stunningly beautiful visuals and voices from around the globe. It is $10 to attend but we will be having photographer, refreshments, and giving away almost $500 in prizes! It is a mom's night out, but anyone is welcome to attend. </description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3647</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2015 21:12:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TOMA Marketing Discussion 11/12/2015 </title><description>Are you "Top of Mind"? Join us for another session of our very popular TOMA Marketing Roundtable discussion. Business owners and managers from all industries meet to discuss various marketing options. What works, what doesn't and what gets in the way. Free for members. </description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3631</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2015 14:46:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kishwaukee United Way Annual Taste of The Vine 11/12/2015 5:30 PM - 11/12/2015 9:00 </title><description>Kishwaukee United Way's signature Taste of the Vine event will be held Thursday, November 12th from 5:30 pm to 9:00 pm at St. Mary’s Memorial Hall (322 Waterman Street, Sycamore). The evening will offer wine samplings, an upscale catered cuisine and a large variety of amazing silent auction gift baskets. Tickets for the event are $40/person. To sponsor this VIP event, to donate a gift basket or service, or to secure tickets, call 815.756.7522. 
</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3443</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2015 14:21:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Services' Pie Auction 11/19/2015 6:00 PM - 11/19/2015 8:30 PM</title><description>Pies and gift baskets are auctioned off to community members to benefit Family Service Agency's Senior Services.</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3646</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2015 20:26:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarantine: The Field Trip Presented by STEM Read 11/19/2015 9:00 AM - 11/19/2015 2:00 PM</title><description>Join NIU STEM Read for our most terrifyingly educational field trip yet! Students and school groups in grade 8 and up can--

 -Experience a day-long, live-action game based on "Quarantine: The Loners" by Lex Thomas
 -Work in groups to solve hands-on challenges related to microbiology, human health, disaster management, costume design, engineering, and economics
 -Meet authors Lex Hrabe and Tom Voorhies
 -Learn from experts from NIU and Argonne National Lab

 Note that this field trip will contain loud noises, flashing lights, disaster simulations, and colored hair spray. Students should wear sneakers and clothes they don't mind getting dirty.

 $10 per student includes registration and pizza party lunch.
 
 Check in begins at 8:30AM

 Learn more and register at stemread.com/fieldtrips</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3620</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2015 20:02:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NIU SOTD Fall 2015 Dance Concert 11/19/2015 7:30 PM - 11/22/2015 10:30 PM</title><description>Fall 2015 Dance Concert
The fall dance production features a cornucopia of performance styles from classic to
modern ballet and everything in between, all choreographed by faculty of the School
of Theatre and Dance. The Esmeralda Ballet will be restaged by Judith Chitwood, a
contemporary ballet restaged by Rich Grund, with additional modern works mounted by
Paula Frasz and Autumn Eckman. The production will also feature a remount of the Bill T.
Jones/Arnie Zale Dance Company choreographed modern work, Days Spent Out Yonder,
which was performed by SoTD this past spring at the Ruth Page Center for the Arts in
Chicago. The production features a new work choreographed to the music of Handel,
called “Drama Queens.”
Performances
Thursday, November 19 7:30pm
Friday, November 20 7:30pm
Saturday, November 21 7:30pm
Sunday, November 22 2:00pm</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3626</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2015 13:30:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>STEM Divas Virtual Reality 11/21/2015 9:00 AM - 11/21/2015 1:00 PM</title><description>This class is for our STEM Divas that are curious about animation, computers, video games and how they all work together. They will learn the essentials of video game design while developing a story to design their own game. STEMDivas will be able to develop basic virtual space and create sound effects while having fun at our own NIU Digital Convergence Lab. Recommended ages 7 and up.  
$39 for one class session 
</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3561</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2015 16:34:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>STEM Divas Virtual Reality 11/21/2015 9:00 AM - 11/21/2015 1:00 PM</title><description>This class is for our STEM Divas that are curious about animation, computers, video games and how they all work together. They will learn the essentials of video game design while developing a story to design their own game. STEMDivas will be able to develop basic virtual space and create sound effects while having fun at our own NIU Digital Convergence Lab. Recommended ages 7 and up.  
$39 for one class session 
</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3562</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2015 16:34:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chemistry Investigations 11/21/2015 9:00 AM - 11/21/2015 12:00 PM</title><description>This is one class that’s sure to get a reaction!  Come get a hands-on look at some basic chemistry as students perform fun and easy experiments that will teach them about chemical reactions.  We’ll be doing experiments with acids &amp; bases, liquid nitrogen, tie dye, and even making our own glow in the dark slime! Students should also bring an item from home to tie dye. Items should be 100% cotton for best results. Recommend for ages 10 and up. This is a 2-part class. The second class takes place on December 5th. 
$59 for 2-class session 
</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3563</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2015 16:35:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>3D Printing Mania 11/21/2015 9:00 AM - 11/21/2015 12:00 PM</title><description>What is 3D printing? Where is 3D printing used? How do you 3D print? Get an answer to all of these questions in our new 3D printing class led by experienced engineers. Learn how to use CAD software to create your own personal figurine to take home, anything from action figures and toy cars to bracelets and toy pets. This is a 2-part class. The second class takes place on December 5th. 
Morning Session: 9:00am- 12.00pm OR Afternoon session 1.00pm-4.00pm. 
$79 for 2-class session. </description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3564</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2015 16:36:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Women In To Light 12/2/2015 7:30 PM - 12/6/2015 9:30 PM</title><description>NIU's Production of Women In To Light- Freshman BFA Showcase
Women Into Light is a “derived piece,” developed as a cooperative work between actors and
directorial staff expressly for the purpose of creating deeper characterizations, through physicality and
acting, and a deeper understanding of the real lives of women who have never been portrayed on
the stage. Based on research of journals, autobiographies and diaries, the stories will highlight the life
histories of forgotten women who have been either overlooked or covered up by history.

Performances:
Wednesday, December 2 @ 7:30 pm
Thursday, December 3 @ 7:30 pm
Saturday, December 5 @ 2:00 pm
Saturday, December 5 @ 7:30 pm
Sunday, December 6 @ 2:00 </description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3633</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2015 17:22:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CSA Showcase Recital 12/5/2015 9:00 AM - 12/5/2015 </title><description>This recital features children and adult students who take private lessons on a variety of instruments.  A reception will follow the performance.

This event is free and open to the public.</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3599</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2015 17:01:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CSA Showcase Recital 12/5/2015 11:00 AM - 12/5/2015 </title><description>This recital features children and adult students who take private lessons on a variety of instruments.  A reception will follow the performance.

This event is free and open to the public.</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3600</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2015 17:01:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CSA Students of Georgia Price 12/5/2015 3:00 PM - 12/5/2015 </title><description>Come hear the piano students of Georgia Price play in the Recital Hall at the NIU Music Building.  A reception will follow the performance.

This recital is free and open to the public.</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3601</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2015 17:02:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CSA Guitar Students of Eric Schroeder 12/5/2015 5:00 PM - 12/5/2015 </title><description>Come hear the guitar students of Eric Schroeder play in the Recital Hall at the NIU Music Building.  The program features both solo and group pieces.  A reception will follow the performance.

This recital is free and open to the public.</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3602</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2015 17:03:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CSA Steelband and NIUkulele Ensemble Concert 12/5/2015 7:00 PM - 12/5/2015 </title><description>Come hear the fun tunes and rhythms of the CSA Steelband, directed by Yuko Asada, and the NIUkulele Ensemble, directed by Eric Schroeder.  The groups will play separately and then collaborate at the end for a musical finale.  A reception will follow the performance.

This concert is free and open to the public.</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3603</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 13:45:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CSA Students of Jaina Krueger 12/6/2015 12:00 PM - 12/6/2015 </title><description>Come hear the harp and piano students of Jaina Krueger play in the Recital Hall at the NIU Music Building.  A reception will follow the performance.

This recital is free and open to the public.</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3604</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 13:46:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CSA Suzuki Students of Tom Cappaert 12/6/2015 2:00 PM - 12/6/2015 </title><description>This recital features the Suzuki cello students of Tom Cappaert.  A reception will follow the performance.

This recital is free and open to the public.</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3605</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 13:46:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CSA Students of Marilyn Montzka 12/7/2015 5:30 PM - 12/7/2015 </title><description>Come hear the Suzuki piano students of Marilyn Montzka perform in the NIU Recital Hall. A reception will follow the performance.

This recital is free and open to the public.</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3606</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 13:46:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CSA Symphonette Concert 12/8/2015 6:00 PM - 12/8/2015 </title><description>Come hear young musicians from the area perform together in the NIU Concert Hall. Linc Smelser directs the CSA Symphonette Ensemble. A reception will follow the performance.

This event is free and open to the public.</description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3607</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 13:47:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CSA Children's Choir Concert 12/9/2015 7:00 PM - 12/9/2015 </title><description>The CSA Children's Choir will perform a variety of pieces at their winter concert in the NIU Music Building.  This ensemble is directed by Mary Lynn Doherty.  A reception will follow the performance.

This event is free and open to the public. </description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3608</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 13:48:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CSA Guitar Ensemble Recital 12/9/2015 8:00 PM - 12/9/2015 </title><description>This performance features the CSA Guitar Ensemble directed by Quentin Dover.  A reception will follow the performance.

This recital is free and open to the public. </description><link>http://www.dekalb.org/wcevents/eventdetail.aspx?EventID=3609</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 13:48:29 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>